GRAB SUN JAE AND RUN
SUMMER 2013
The program "Friends of Ten-Ten" is on air.
and I'm the host Hyun.
Today our guest is the inimitable
Ryu Sung Jae from Eclipse.
The summer heat has finally replaced
rain and cool weather.
Great time to listen
Eclipse's song "Torrential Rain".
Did you know that this particular song
most often associated with first love?
This was a revelation for me.
Did you write it before your debut?
- Yes.
- That's how it is.
Probably inspired you
your first love?
Judging by the reaction, I was not mistaken.
Your new film also reveals
theme of first love.
- Yes.
- Tell us about your first love.
This will remain between us, I give you my word.
About first love?
When we met...
it was raining.
Uncle!
She smiled under a yellow umbrella.
And it took my breath away.
It seems...
I then forgot how to breathe.
Come on. And he said that the fans -
his first love.
This...
-...secret.
- Who is she?
Curious.
SERIES 6
Is this why you sang in front of a whole audience?
I didn't do anything for you!
Girlfriend.
Come with me.
Have you seen Taesung?
Crap. Choi Ga Hyun took Seol somewhere!
What's wrong with him? You idiot, why did you come here?
Tae Sung will figure it out.
I won't leave it like this!
What if they touch her?
Get it!
What's wrong with you?
I warned you.
Don't hurt my Salt! Did you warn me?
- What?
- You don't even like me.
You got tired of Ga Hyun and decided
switch to someone.
At me?
- Who said?
- It doesn't matter.
I knew you were an idiot
but not that much.
Some kind of nightmare.
It's a pity that I realized this now.
In general, everything is over between us, asshole.
Do you understand me?
Now you are still very young,
but you can’t live like that.
By the way.
I'm saying this just in case.
If suddenly I start running after you
and repeat that I don’t remember anything,
don't pay attention.
Got it?
Yes. Everything is correct.
You need to study, what kind of relationship?
This is my idol!
You start again.
Let's go. It's time already.
What?
Still?
Wow. Straight from the picture.
Can you still move?
Funny. Very fun.
How to remove it?
Song Jae...
Should I think about myself?
Will you break up?
If I want this, will you break up?
Salt.
Leave Kim Tae-sung.
You...
I like you.
What?
Does Sun Jae like me?
- Did you hit yourself?
- Can't be!
Or did someone hit you?
Lim Sol!
Salt.
You...
I like you.
Why do I remember?
What's the matter, seriously?
And really, what's the matter?
- What?
- Why didn’t you like the onion?
You did the same thing.
Did something happen?
No. Nothing.
But my eyes are burning!
You touched the onions, but didn’t wash your hands -
Certainly!
Here, keep it in your mouth.
Still burning.
Tears flow like a river, but she continues to sit.
Okay, get up.
Go to the store and get some makgeolli.
I just forgot.
For what?
I knew you were an idiot
but not that much.
Some kind of nightmare. In general, between us
It's over, asshole.
Do you understand me?
What are you thinking about?
Strange.
What?
- This is it.
- This is it?
How to say...
Something... It's like...
- As if?
- Hurts.
- Heart?
- Heart.
After such a thrashing I should
headache.
- Heart?
- Tell?
I understand! You're angry because Lim Seol
abandoned you.
Everything is burning inside you.
It doesn't give you any peace!
That's why my heart hurts!
Tired of living?
Blockhead.
Crap.
You're a fool, Sung Jae. Fool.
By what right do you point it out to her?
Why should I watch her
dating someone else?
You didn't even confess to her.
How can you say such a thing?
A tough nut to crack.
You won't give in.
I'm already tired!
Listen. Forget it.
I'll introduce you to someone.
- Let's go, let's go.
- Let go.
Let's go, Sung Jae.
Will you introduce me?
- Crap!
- Stop. Stop!
Fell in love?
Screw you.
- In that case...
- No need, Sung Jae.
Let's forget about Lim Sol.
You'll meet someone better!
God. God.
What's wrong with you?
Have you been abandoned?
Are you kidding me?
- God.
- Good luck.
Let's.
Come on. Great. Great!
Song Jae!
Is he stupid?
Jerk.
How long did you cry?
What?
Wait.
Don't cry!
He's not worth your tears!
What?
What are you talking about? I...
I'm crying because of onions.
Luke?
Kim Tae Sun - bow?
What?
Are you drinking again?
Do you drink because it's hard?
Just...
tell me!
Why drink right away?
No. This is not it...
Not what you thought, Sung Jae.
Give it back.
In terms of? Give it here!
No, you're hurting yourself.
What do you mean, I'll hit you? Give it back!
I won't give it up! Alcohol is not the answer.
Give it back, Sung Jae! Give it back!
Are you serious? I won't give it up, I won't give it up!
What's wrong with you?
What?
- I'm pouring it out.
- What are you doing? This is for grandma!
What a freak.
Hands off!
Stand!
God!
Who is he to touch my sister?
Song Jae!
Geum, are you crazy?
Crap.
Song Jae!
- Delicious.
- So.
Maybe we should take him to the hospital?
Which hospital?
McColley got drunk and fell asleep.
Salt, Salt. Tell me, is this somehow ugly?
It's all because of you, Geum!
He never drank makgeolli.
A couple of drops got into my mouth,
and he passed out.
Sung Jae must be very hot.
You sleep like a baby. Come on.
Salt.
You...
I like you.
What?
Where am I?
Go crazy.
Sorry.
What are you...
I wanted...
Fan! I wanted to turn on the fan.
My God!
Where does the fan come from?
What? Did you turn over in your sleep?
OK. Spit.
It suddenly became cold.
Is he so strong even in his sleep?
Oh my God, it's cold.
OK.
Did you fall asleep?
What are you doing there?
God.
Come on. Did you fall asleep right here?
Am I sleepwalking?
You assholes, I'm now...
Come here! Come here! Come here!
Come here...
Hey, let me go! Let me go! Let me go!
Why the hell are you so strong?
Come into the hall, why are you sitting here?
Did they confess to you?
- How did you know?
- Seriously? And who?
Ryu Sung Jae?
Does Sun Jae like me?
Does such a bright guy like me?
You made him fall in love with you.
I?
When?
Just think about it.
Buried in the middle of training
you said that you love him.
You for every competition
came to support him.
And when he was in the hospital,
brought him food.
I had a good reason for this.
What follows is a complete nightmare!
I snuck into his room,
while he was sleeping.
Everything is clear! You learned from an adult fox.
Not the fox, but she is clearly older.
And you can’t tell from it
that he is interested in something other than sports.
These guys can't resist
assertive girls!
Is it true?
The problem is that you're yanking it!
If you don't want to go to the toilet, don't take off your pants.
If you don't like it, don't pull it!
Don't you want to go to the toilet? In terms of?
What?
Don't be a fool, go learn!
Did I really make him fall in love with me?
Can you be quieter?
- Sung Jae...
- Yes?
What are you doing here?
- I wanted...
- You can't confess to her
after the breakup.
Don't show it! Don't blur!
Be calm.
...to see you.
I came to study.
Yes.
Get busy.
Come on. And he immediately sat down next to you.
Coincidence?
Maybe.
Salt.
Try your best.
Fine. I'll try.
You... You... You try too.
Did you arrange a date for yourself?
Run, run, run!
Crap! How is that possible?
How can you screw up?
I lost my phone.
Yes, by the way.
They say Choi Ga Young won't leave
Lim Sol at rest.
He constantly runs after her.
What? And you're just talking now?
I found out today.
Jerk.
Get out of here.
Stupid.
OUR SNACK
RYU SUN JAE'S REPORT CARD
And what are you going to do?
With the eighth level.
Which one do I need?
Am I way behind?
You're not just falling behind - you're at the bottom.
This is the first round, that's enough
passing level.
- And what level is this?
- Fifth.
What about your eighth?
Eighth?
Come on, kill it!
What do you mean, score? How?
Eighth level!
Wow. This is the level.
Lee Seung Yup is in good shape.
Yes, of course...
but exams are just around the corner,
need to concentrate.
You promised to help.
Yes, I promised.
But I haven’t prepared myself for a long time
for exams!
I don't remember how the root is extracted,
How can I help?
Spit it out.
Faster! You'll get burned.
Not hot?
Everything is fine.
Scored!
I mean, I scored, what are you talking about? What did you score?
Look, he scored!
- Lee Seung Yeop! Lee Seung Yup! Lee Seung Yup!
- Lee Seung Yeop!
- Second point? Wow...
Korea, go! Korea, go!
What? Rain?
I have an umbrella. I took it in the morning.
Where is he? Stayed in the hall?
I forgot it in the cafe.
Where are you going? It's already raining.
Who else is pulling who? Don't even know.
You almost hit yourself.
He plays with my heart, he really does!
What? Have we won?
Maybe.
Wow. So, we made it to the finals.
What are you thinking?
What? Nothing.
It's all because of Taesung.
She's sad.
Do you want...
Shall we go outside to get sick?
On the street?
The problem is that you're yanking it!
Exams are coming soon, we need to prepare.
Is it possible to sit at that desk every day?
sit in the reading room?
Sometimes you need a distraction
to fresh air.
At least for a day.
No?
If you remember all the words
from the English dictionary.
Only then!
All the words?
Clear. So you don't want to.
So get busy studying.
What if I remember everything?
You said you would agree.
One day is enough for me.
Let's go.
What?
Whatever he can think of.
Him again?
The rain has stopped.
Why do you need an umbrella?
Are you stuck?
-Where did you go for a walk?
- What do you want?
What's happened?
Let's talk.
- I have nothing to say.
- I have something.
Listen.
- She doesn't want to.
- Go away.
First you.
God. Should I have been scared?
Okay, okay.
What did you want to say?
Wait.
What?
Be calm.
Then go straight home.
See you tomorrow.
- Bye!
- Let's.
Enough. Forget me.
- What are you talking about?
- Forget me!
How can I forget?
Fool...
Yes, Kim Tae Sun is a fool.
It's my fault.
If loving you is a crime.
Tae Sung!
If love is a crime
then I'll be behind bars.
You're crazy.
Lim Sol.
You are my star!
No.
Crap!
What do you have?
I'm very busy, let's hurry up.
Choi Ga Hyun is pestering you.
I didn't know.
Are you badly hurt?
- I cried a lot.
- No! I didn't cry at all!
Didn't you cry? Why?
Crying over a jerk like you?
Of course not.
It's strange, but I was upset.
Why?
That's it.
OK. Sorry.
That's what I wanted to say.
I'm really sorry.
Well, it's not all that scary.
And I didn't use you.
- Why did you meet with me?
- You like me.
You're with everyone you like
are you dating?
- No.
- And how can we believe your words?
- What?
Maybe...
is it mutual?
- What are you...
- Yes.
I liked you.
Wow.
Listen to him. You're so funny!
What to do?
I really like you.
Enough! Do you want to return the bear -
return and go home!
Don't want!
In terms of? Do you want to throw it away?
Give it here.
Give it back! I won't throw it away.
This is a gift from a loved one.
Now they walk like that!
What nonsense? Give it here!
No, no, no. I won't give it up! No.
Daesung, our love is eternal!
Maybe we can get together? Let's?
No!
Probably my worst enemy is myself.
What's happened?
My legs are numb.
What?
God.
My God. What a son I have!
Exemplary! Exemplary!
His legs are numb, but he continues
help my father, work.
God. You've grown so much, you've grown so much.
Son, did you know?
Plants also have ears.
That's why we need them every day
iron like this
and speak good words to them.
Beautiful, beautiful.
- And then...
- Where is she? Ran away with him?
Now I and Sun Jae will only praise.
Wow, son, you...
You shameless puppy! What is this, a weed?
You haven't pulled out all the weeds yet,
but he got to my pepper!
Go away, go away, go away!
I asked you to help, but you ruined everything!
God! My God, my God, my God,
what to do?
Excuse me, pepper, excuse me. God!
- Dad!
- My God. God!
What should I do now?
Why do you get into fights?
I need to finish school
otherwise you will regret it later.
Tasty?
Me too, eternal.
Mother!
God.
Mom, where are you going?
I told you yesterday.
To Jeju with friends.
- Jeju?
- Yes.
She left with that uncle.
Today?
Abandoning your daughter-graduate
and you leave for Jeju with a man,
who gave you a lift?
Who cares?
When did you become so important?
I raised you and your brother alone.
Can't I rest anymore?
I just feel sorry for dad!
He worried about you until his death,
I thought about you, but I couldn’t
leave in peace!
Wash school shirts by hand
every day, understand?
Don't throw colored things into the car
for quick wash
otherwise they will get dirty!
Okay, okay.
And also soak the dishes after eating.
Are you used to leaving food on your plates?
That's why all the flies flock to us!
And call your brother.
He gets drunk every night
He might even fall asleep on the street.
What if the police come?
Don't forget to close the door
and windows at night.
I got it, mom!
Do you think we are small?
You are adults, but you have no brains!
It's because you're constantly
you're following us
and we can cope without you.
Is it true?
Have you grown up, are you better off without your mother now?
Of course it's better!
Like this. She brought it up and is no longer needed.
Finally got it?
They say that in old age you search
support from my husband.
Find a man.
Yes? In old age you have to die.
What kind of man?
That's enough. Don't talk nonsense.
I went. Learn!
Have a nice rest, mom!
That is, neither today nor tomorrow,
namely September 1
could something happen to you?
And you want to tell, but you can’t?
Yes. That's right.
My God. Wow...
Girl. If you think what's wrong with you
something will happen at the reservoir,
don't go there.
You're right, but...
Yes, yes. So.
Here you go. Eat some candy and go home.
Understood?
- Yes.
- Let's.
Maybe you're just tired, don't worry!
And the main thing is that everything is fine.
Detective Kim.
What's happened? What could happen?
This is nonsense.
What do you have?
Give me the night watch log
per month.
So, the submission...
- Yes!
- How did he catch that ball? Master!
- My God, what a great guy!
- Victory!
Hello?
If you call, at least answer!
I...
I found the phone.
Exactly, exactly! This is my granddaughter.
You probably found it.
How can I give it to you?
Let's meet. Where to go?
No.
I'm out of town.
Then can you send it by mail?
I'll tell you the address now.
Let's.
COLLECTION OF EXERCISES
What a study...
How long ago have you come?
This is my idol!
Salt.
You...
I like you.
"My friend is hungry."
"Look".
So? "Look, look."
Am I crazy?
What?
No. No, nothing.
Why...
are you all red?
Hot simple.
You...
do you know everything?
What?
Did you notice?
Noticed what?
I...
learned all the words.
- What?
- You promised
that we will go out into the street to get sick.
If you don't believe me, ask.
No, no, I believe it.
Then we'll go.
I...
I'll tell you something.
Go Korea!
It's getting hot on the streets!
Tens of thousands of people came out to cheer
for the Korean team!
Eight out of eight!
Will our team succeed?
which constantly puts
world records,
win first in Korean history
baseball gold?
Go Korea!
- Lim Sol, here!
- Go ahead, Korea!
Go Korea!
Allow me. I'll pass.
Allow me.
- Skip it.
- Thank you.
You're early!
Yes. I wanted to take a seat.
- You can see from here.
- Is it true? Isn't it hot?
You can live.
And then I almost died.
And don't talk. It's very hot.
Is that better?
Hyun Joo has arrived!
Hello.
Geum, are you home?
Where did Salt go?
You know better.
Our Hyun Joo brought chicken!
Sol and I wanted to watch the Games.
No salt, I'll go.
Don't go.
But if you leave...
leave the chicken.
Baseball competition within
Games 2008...
What kind of octopus?
Oh, are you talking about this?
That's enough!
How old is Choi Min Sik? Boring.
They didn't take you?
Thought the actors' directors
do they choose based on makeup?
Sincerity is important here!
Exactly.
After so many failures
I decided to stand out.
You're right. God...
I just want to feel sorry for him.
Come to your senses! This is too much!
Yes! Serve it up, yeah!
Crap.
Hyun Joo. Why don't you eat?
Here you go. Eat.
How caring. Cute.
Come to your senses! This is too much!
Hyun Joo, look.
Clean.
Let no one, seeing this bone,
won’t understand what kind of chicken it was:
fried or baked.
Did his words touch me?
This is the most disgusting person
in the world - Lim Geum.
But he's so cute.
No, this is too much!
- Lee Seung Yup...
- Don't cross the line!
And the decisive one...
Don't cross! No way!
He went over the line. Out of line!
- Did you go beyond the line?
- He went beyond the line!
Out! Eat! Lee Seung Yup hits a home run!
Hyun Joo! Come here! We can win!
We can win!
Lee Seung Yup! Home run! Go crazy!
- I stepped over.
- Yes. Hello, sunshine.
Geum is watching baseball.
Your princess is busy right now.
Yes! Yes? Tomorrow? Kiss!
- What?
- Do you have a girlfriend?
Yes.
- Why?
- God.
What, I can't date?
It is forbidden!
Why were you silent?
Hyun Joo! Where are you going?
Get him off the screen! Away!
Runs, runs, but, unfortunately,
goes over the line!
- What a pity!
- Out of line!
The player is speeding up!
Get ready!
LEE YONG GYU
Lee Young Gyu! Lee Young Gyu!
- Lee Young Gyu!
Beat it off! Beat it off! Beat it off! Beat it off!
Lee Young Kyu brings another point to the team,
now the score is 3:1.
Lee Young Gyu! Lee Young Gyu! Lee Young Gyu!
SALT AND DAESON
Listen. Your father is so busy
that can't even visit you?
Korea leads with a score of 3:2.
The streets of the capital were filled
happy fans.
Look. It's Sol and Sung Jae!
Wow. You should learn from him
smart guy.
I immediately came to my senses
how I met the one.
Tell?
- Come out.
- What?
Get out. Get up and get out of here. Here you go.
- What's wrong with you?
- Leave. Get out of here, asshole. Leave!
- Let me go, what is it?
- Leave!
I'll go myself.
How aggressive you are.
So now comes the decisive blow!
Take a position, get ready.
And hit! Hit!
- Let's!
- Right to the point!
And this is a victory! Victory!
Korea took gold! Incredible!
Korea won!
Go Korea!
- Go ahead, Korea!
- Let's leave.
What? I can't hear!
What?
What's happened?
I wanted to wait some more...
but I can't do it anymore.
You know what I don't like?
Rain.
I spent days swimming...
but I just hated getting wet
in the rain.
But...
we met in the rain.
I liked it.
I liked what I hated.
And this was not only...
that day.
I love rain.
And I will continue to love him.
And him...
...and you.
Salt.
You tell me...
I like you very much.
No, I...
I don't expect an answer right away.
Song Jae...
I...
Damn.
Answer.
This is something important.
- Hello?
- This is Kim Tae Sun.
Are you with Sol now?
Why do you suddenly...
- Let's go.
- What?
What's happened?
Your mom is now...
in the hospital.
What?
- Excuse me, can I see Pak Pok Soon?
-Your name is Sol?
Didn't recognize me?
We met once.
Don't you remember?
Your mother is being examined now.
Wait outside for now.
Fortunately, after the operation
everything will be fine.
And I didn't even know.
Why?
And we can cope without you,
We are no longer little children!
Is it true? Grew up, now you
Is it better without a mother?
Of course it's better!
I said we could manage without her.
It turns out that my mother was sick.
It's not your fault.
Don't even think about it.
Thanks for calling.
If it weren't for you, mom would be completely alone.
- How is she?
- The operation has begun.
Everything is fine.
What happened to your good hand?
Got into a fight with someone again?
No.
Who do you even take me for?
It's good that no.
Tae Son.
I don't know what wounds you have in your heart.
But...
so as not to regret later, come on now
Let's forget all the old grievances.
That's what I want to say
your first love.
So I ask...
change your destiny.
And I will pray for you.
Bye!
What's wrong with her?
Why is he saying goodbye?
I'm giving you some painkillers.
If it becomes intolerable, tell me.
Thank you.
- Where is grandma?
- He and Geum went home.
They'll sleep and come.
- Don’t worry, sleep, mom.
- Well done.
Have you come again?
Operation...
was it successful?
Yes.
Were you asleep?
You look...
...doesn't matter.
Everything is fine.
Have you eaten?
- Let's go.
- Everything is fine, really.
You go.
OK. I won't accompany you
but I'll come again tomorrow.
No.
Don't come.
Song Jae.
I don't feel anything.
Here's how.
I was expecting something else.
- It's so cold.
-You're just confused. It's because of me.
- No.
- Sorry for giving you false hope.
- No!
- You see...
It's hard for me next to you.
So please...
stop loving me.
Exactly! I forgot about the main thing!
How do you feel?
I? I'm leaving soon.
Where?
Whether to another city or abroad -
I'm not talking about that.
How do you really feel?
DAY OF THE ACCIDENT
Dear sister, don't you want to
bring your brother's phone?
- I forgot him...
- Now?
Mom will be discharged tomorrow. Be patient for one night.
They should call me about
one audition.
Well? Please!
You didn't go to school today anyway,
and you're too lazy to help?
Sorry, Geum.
But I'm not going out today.
So come and get it yourself.
Or wait until tomorrow.
Yes. Two hours left.
Carefully. Without incident.
You forgot your umbrella.
Don't go to the reading room because of me?
I won't interfere. Let's talk.
Not for long.
I'll be waiting for you on the site.
Sorry.
I won't go out.
Don't wait for me.
YOU SENT A MESSAGE TO RYU SUN JAE
Where is he going?
Didn't read it?
Is he really waiting for me?
Haven’t we met before those competitions?
We met. You somehow mixed me up
with courier.
Don't remember?
Uncle!
It was raining when we met.
She smiled under a yellow umbrella.
And it took my breath away.
Really...
We met in the rain.
I liked it.
Salt.
You tell me...
I like you very much.
Since then...
GRAB SUN JAE AND RUN
You can't go too far, Sung Jae!
I know everything can change.
- Here, here!
- Young woman? Name!
Any destiny can be changed,
if you want, right?
- Yes?
- What's happened?
Come quickly!
What if the movie doesn't come out because of you?
We need to take Ryu Sung Jae!
Who are you? Do we know each other?
No!
No.
Don't come, Sung Jae!
Translated and voiced by the studio
"Mobile TV"
commissioned by the online cinema Ivy
in 2024.